(Leonard:)that's totally not
how it fake happened.
(Leonard:)Oh...
(Penny:)Okay, whatever.
(Penny:)Will you please just play along
until my dad leaves?
(Leonard:)Hold on, you actually want me
(Leonard:)to deceive your father
with some sort of
(Leonard:)sham play acting and kissing?
'Cause I'm good with that.
(Penny's Dad:)Penny, you out here?
(Penny:)Come on, honey,
not in front of my dad.
(Penny's Dad:)Relax, I've seen you do
a lot worse with a lot stupider.
(Leonard:)See?
(Leonard:)He doesn't mind.
(Penny's Dad:)So, Leonard,
I'm taking your gal out
for a steak dinner;
you want to join us?
(Penny:)Oh, Dad, that's nice,
but Leonard has to work.
(Penny:)Right, Leonard?
(Leonard:)Uh, I do, I
have to work.
(Leonard:)But I'm gonna blow that
off to spend the evening
(Leonard:)with my sweetie and her
father, 'cause, you know,
(Leonard:)just the kind of
boyfriend I am.
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Leonard:)Come here, you.
(Howard:)C-7.
(Raj:)Miss.
(Howard:)How could that be a miss?